Dedaldino da Conceição C. Papelo

Kelsonpapelo18@gmail.com

Tel: 939736657

PERSONAL STATEMENT

Enthusiastic in information technology and software engineering, where I have been developing web and desktop applications for over 3 years, using different technologies, I am interested in working with both backend and frontend, and also a strong connection with Relational and non-Relational databases. Relational

EDUCATION

Bachelor Degree of Computer Engineering

Private University of Angola Mach 2017 - Jun 2022

IT Technician

Medium Polytechnic Institute of Geoscience – 2013 / 2015

WORK EXPERIENCE

Trainee

Dep. Computer Engineering UPRA

Dez 2021 - Maio 2022

I worked on the frontend, creating websites and web applications using Reactjs. Development of technical and software solutions, maintenance and updating of websites.

Computer Technician

Tech Solutions

Jan 2014 – April 2016

Development of management applications using C#, Database Modeling with SQL Server, Database integration with C#

github.com/Dedaldino-papelo

dedaldino-papelo.vercel.app

COURSES

Udemy

The Complete Web developer in 2021 - (Javascript, Reactjs, Nodejs, TypeORM)

Udemy

The Web developer Bootcamp – (Javascript, EJS, Nodejs, MongoDB)

Udemy

Complete React Developer in 2022 – (Firebase, GraphQL, GatsbyJS,Redux)

Digital Inovation One

Linux in 2022

ITEL Training Center

Web Programming (HTML, CSS, Javascript, PHP, MySQL)

CodeCademy

Nodejs Intermediário - (Core Modules, Rest API, NPM)

TRAININGS

Rockeatseat (Ignite Lab)

Advanced Reactis

SKILLS

HTML / CSS / Javascript / C#

Reactis / Nodeis

Git / GitHub

SQL Server / MySQL / PostgreSQL

Bootstrap / SASS

IDIOMAS

Portuguese – Fluent